(Amy:)No one's talking
about Sonny and Cher.
(Sheldon:)You must be thinking
about Donny and Marie,
(Sheldon:)'cause you and I are clearly
talking about Sonny and Cher.
(Amy:)Sheldon, this has to stop.
(Amy:)I know it's hard.
(Amy:)It's hard for me, too.
(Amy:)But I've seen
and talked to you more
(Amy:)in the two days
we've been broken up
(Amy:)than in the last two months
that we were together.
(Sheldon:)Well, if you want
to see less of me,
(Sheldon:)maybe we should go out again.
(Raj:)I can't believe you made out
with Mandy Chao.
(Leonard:)Trust me,
I wish it never happened.
(Raj:)And you knew about this
this whole time?
(Howard:)I did.
(Raj:)And you didn't think to tell me?
(Howard:)Leonard asked me
to keep it to myself.
(Raj:)Let's leave Leonard
out of this for the moment.
(Raj:)This is about you and me.
(Leonard:)Wait, wait, wait, how is my
day-old marriage falling apart
(Leonard:)becoming about you two?
(Raj:)Hang on.
(Raj:)What do I need to do
to make you trust me?
(Howard:)You think it's hard
having one wife,
(Howard:)try having two.